//Create Questions
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is Atwood's Law?",
        answer: "'Any application that can be written in Javascript will eventually be written in Javascript.'",
        options: [
            "'Any application that can be written in Javascript will eventually be written in Javascript.'",
            "'Anything that can go wrong in programming will go wrong'",
            "'Javascript is eight steps sideways, one step forward'",
            "'The worst Javascript is better than the best of the rest'"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What is syntax?",
        answer: "Proper arrangement of words within the rules of a programming language",
        options: [
            "An object-based programming language based on events and functions",
            "The meaning of the code as interpreted by the browser",
            "Proper arrangement of words within the rules of a programming language",
            "When you don't do your taxes",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What does JavaScript do for a website?",
        answer: "Functionality/Interactivity",
        options: [
            "Tells the browser how to read the HTML structure",
            "Does styling that can't be achieved in CSS",
            "Functionality/Interactivity",
            "None of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which of the following can you do with a for loop?",
        answer: "Process arrays",
        options: [
            "Tell the browser how to interpret the HTML",
            "Process arrays",
            "Pair with a while loop to create a meta-matrix grid structure",
            "None of the above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question : "Which of the following are the building blocks of Javascript applications?",
        answer: "Objects",
        options: [
            "For loops",
            "While loops",
            "Console.log",
            "Objects",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question : "Which of the following cannot be used to declare a variable?",
        answer: "Set",
        options: [
            "Let",
            "Const",
            "Set",
            "Var",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question : "Which of the following is not a way to introduce commands to be executed?",
        answer: "Function Introduction",
        options: [
            "Function Declaration",
            "Function Introduction",
            "Function Expression",
            "None of the Above",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question : "Which of the following is true about variable naming conventions in JavaScript?",
        answer: "Both of the above.",
        options: [
            "You should not use any of the JavaScript reserved keyword as variable name.",
            "JavaScript variable names should not start with a numeral (0-9).",
            "Both of the above.",
            "None of the above.",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question : "Which of the following is not a Javascript data type??",
        answer: "Decimal",
        options: [
            "Boolean",
            "Number",
            "BigInt",
            "Decimal",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question : "How do you connect your HTML file to your Javascript file?",
        answer: "With a script tag",
        options: [
            "With a link tag",
            "With a source tag",
            "With a script tag",
            "With a connect tag",
        ]
    }
];
